♪ Yeah, listen closely, let me tell you 'bout the flow.
We simplifying everything, it's time to let it go. ♪
We simplifying everything, it's time to let it go.
No more complex stacks, we're cutting through the noise now. ♪
♪ We simplifying everything, it's time to let it go.
No more complex stacks, we're cutting through the noise now.
Backend is the application, listen to the choice now. ♪
♪ No more complex stacks, we're cutting through the noise now.
Backend is the application, listen to the choice now.
Java, Rust, or C#, just write it once and let it be. ♪
♪ Backend is the application, listen to the choice now.
Java, Rust, or C#, just write it once and let it be.
Declarative UI for the world to see, so clean. ♪
♪ Java, Rust, or C#, just write it once and let it be.
Declarative UI for the world to see, so clean.
A proof of concept working from the start to the end. ♪
♪ Declarative UI for the world to see, so clean.
A proof of concept working from the start to the end.
The tests are glowing green and every broken link we mend. ♪
♪ A proof of concept working from the start to the end.
The tests are glowing green and every broken link we mend.
It's language and it's renderer agnostic by design. ♪
♪ The tests are glowing green and every broken link we mend.
It's language and it's renderer agnostic by design.
This protocol is moving with a rhythm so divine. ♪
♪ It's language and it's renderer agnostic by design.
This protocol is moving with a rhythm so divine.
Forget the bundlers, forget the extra build. ♪
♪ This protocol is moving with a rhythm so divine.
Forget the bundlers, forget the extra build.
The frontend contract's over and the promises fulfilled. ♪
♪ Forget the bundlers, forget the extra build.
The frontend contract's over and the promises fulfilled.
We shipping this directly from the server to the screen. ♪
♪ The frontend contract's over and the promises fulfilled.
We shipping this directly from the server to the screen.
The smoothest operation that the world has ever seen. ♪
♪ We shipping this directly from the server to the screen.
The smoothest operation that the world has ever seen.
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT! ♪
♪ The smoothest operation that the world has ever seen.
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT! ♪
♪ PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO! ♪
♪ BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW! ♪
♪ WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT! ♪
♪ LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT! ♪
♪ PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO! ♪
♪ BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW! ♪
♪ WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
Sixteen-byte opcodes passing on the wire. ♪
♪ LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
Sixteen-byte opcodes passing on the wire.
Every single renderer is catching all the fire. ♪
♪ Sixteen-byte opcodes passing on the wire.
Every single renderer is catching all the fire.
No more virtual DOM, no re-rendering cost. ♪
♪ Every single renderer is catching all the fire.
No more virtual DOM, no re-rendering cost.
In the ocean of complexity, we're never getting lost. ♪
♪ No more virtual DOM, no re-rendering cost.
In the ocean of complexity, we're never getting lost.
An unchanged screen transmits zero bytes of data. ♪
♪ In the ocean of complexity, we're never getting lost.
An unchanged screen transmits zero bytes of data.
Only tiny deltas, we'll see you all much later. ♪
♪ An unchanged screen transmits zero bytes of data.
Only tiny deltas, we'll see you all much later.
Spring Boot or Quarkus, just drop the dependency. ♪
♪ Only tiny deltas, we'll see you all much later.
Spring Boot or Quarkus, just drop the dependency.
Running at a smooth sixty frames for you and me. ♪
♪ Spring Boot or Quarkus, just drop the dependency.
Running at a smooth sixty frames for you and me.
The flagship path is SSR, the instant paint is here. ♪
♪ Running at a smooth sixty frames for you and me.
The flagship path is SSR, the instant paint is here.
Everything is native and the vision's crystal clear. ♪
♪ The flagship path is SSR, the instant paint is here.
Everything is native and the vision's crystal clear.
We cutting out the middleman, we cutting out the pain. ♪
♪ Everything is native and the vision's crystal clear.
We cutting out the middleman, we cutting out the pain.
Pathland is the future and it's taking off the chain. ♪
♪ We cutting out the middleman, we cutting out the pain.
Pathland is the future and it's taking off the chain.
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT! ♪
♪ Pathland is the future and it's taking off the chain.
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT! ♪
♪ PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO! ♪
♪ BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW! ♪
♪ WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT! ♪
♪ LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT! ♪
♪ PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO! ♪
♪ BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW! ♪
♪ WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
(Ooh, oh, oh...) We headed to the future now, the vision's very wide. ♪
♪
♪ LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
(Ooh, oh, oh...) We headed to the future now, the vision's very wide.
On mobile and on desktop, there is nowhere left to hide. ♪
♪ (Ooh, oh, oh...) We headed to the future now, the vision's very wide.
On mobile and on desktop, there is nowhere left to hide.
From embedded chips to WASM, compiling to the core. ♪
♪ On mobile and on desktop, there is nowhere left to hide.
From embedded chips to WASM, compiling to the core.
This protocol is opening a brand new shiny door. ♪
♪ From embedded chips to WASM, compiling to the core.
This protocol is opening a brand new shiny door.
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT! ♪
♪ This protocol is opening a brand new shiny door.
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT! ♪
♪ PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO! ♪
♪ BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW! ♪
♪ WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT! ♪
♪ LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT! ♪
♪ PATHLAND IS THE PROTOCOL, WE BRINGING IN THE LIGHT!
BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO! ♪
♪ BINARY UI IS SHINING OH SO BRIGHT!
WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW! ♪
♪ WRITE IT ONCE AND RUN IT EVERYWHERE YOU GO!
LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
Pathland... yeah, you know the vibe. ♪
♪ LET THE WHOLE WORLD FEEL THE PATHLAND FLOW!
Pathland... yeah, you know the vibe.
Binary protocol, we taking over. (Out.) ♪
♪ Pathland... yeah, you know the vibe.